Playful Kiss (Naughty Kiss) YouTube version
惡作劇之吻 Youtube 篇
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at Viki
Subtitles created by the PKer team at www.Viki
Episode 1 Newlywed Morning
第一篇 新婚之日
I realize this even more these days,
我突然发现一些事
when I open up my eyes in the morning,
每个早晨当我睁开眼时
I'm so happy at the mere fact that Seung Jo is next to me.
看到胜祖在我身旁我就很高兴
Though it's already been a year since we got married, I still can't believe it.
真的很难以置信，虽然我们已经结婚一年了
Does Seung Jo feel that way too?
不知道胜祖也会不会这么认为
Good morning.
Good morning （早安）
Did you sleep well?
睡的好吗？
Your stare is blinding.
你的眼神太耀眼了
Even more so than the sunlight.
比阳光还耀眼
It's Sunday.
是礼拜天啊
Let's sleep some more.
我们多睡点吧
I have to get up.
我要起身啊
Everyone went on a trip and it's been a while since we've spent time together, just the two of us.
每个人都去旅行了 我们很久没有单独的相处了
I'm going to make Seung Jo's breakfast myself.
我要亲手做胜祖的早餐
Just 5 minutes.
就五分钟
Fine, just 5 minutes?
好吧 就五分钟
Did you sleep well, Seung Jo?
你睡的好吗 胜祖
The sun hasn't even come up yet, why did you set the alarm so early?!
太阳都还没升起 你干嘛把闹钟调这么早
Don't stare up at me with those swollen eyes!
不要用那双臃肿的眼睛看着我
Everyone went on a trip, so it's a Sunday with just Seung Jo.
每个人都去旅行了 所以是一个只有胜祖的礼拜天
Enjoy a perfect English breakfast just like in the movies.
像电影般的享受着英式早餐
Clean the house with Seung Jo until it's sparkling clean!
与胜祖一起把房子打扫一番
I want to show everyone the image of a perfect daughter-in-law.
我要给每个人看一看完美的媳妇
I also plan on watching a romantic comedy with Seung Jo.
我还要跟胜祖看一部浪漫爱情篇
I'm so looking forward to today!
真是令人期待啊
What are you looking for, new bride?
新媳妇找些什么啊
New bride!
新媳妇
Me?!
我吗？
Then what other new bride is there?
不然还有谁啊
New bride?
新媳妇
That's right, I'm a new bride!
恩 我是新媳妇
It's fresh, what do you think?
很新鲜的 你觉得怎样
If you boil and marinate it, it's really good!
如果拿来煮 很好吃的噢
Your husband will enjoy it!
你老公一定会喜欢的
Please give this to me.
给我这个吧
And this one, and that one, and that one! Please give me one of each!
还有这个 那个 还有那个 都给我各一个吧
New bride!
新媳妇
Yes?
什么？
Go enjoy these with your husband. They're apples.
这个跟你老公一起吃吧 是苹果
Thank you!
谢谢你
No, no, no!
不行 不行 不行！
What are you doing?!
干嘛啊！
Why are you eating this? Do you know how important breakfast is?
你怎么吃这个啊 你不知道早餐的重要性吗
Then again, where did you go at the break of dawn?
对了 你一大早跑去哪里了
Are you going to make a feast for breakfast?
你要弄丰富的早餐吗
Just leave it up to me. Do you know how much I've looked forward to it being just the two of us?
就交给我吧 你不知道我有多期待只有我们的周末
Do you think you can do it by yourself?
你认为你一个人行吗
You're not going to starve me, are you?
不要让我饿肚子哦
But I'm still a new bride.
我可是新媳妇
There's no way I'll starve my hubby.
不会让我老公饿肚子的
New bride?
新媳妇？
Hubby?
老公？
I'll prepare breakfast, so hubby, please go wash up.
我会准备早餐的 所以老公 你帮忙打扫吧
Hey.
喂
Are you trying to play the role of newlyweds just like in dramas?
你是不是在学电影里的新婚夫妇？
We are newlyweds.
我们本来就是新婚夫妇嘛
Stop dilly-dallying. Hurry and go up.
不要说了 快去吧
I put the laundry in the washer so start it for me too!
我把衣服放进洗衣机了你帮我按钮就可以了
Let's just eat out.
我们还是出去吃吧
Please just go up.
你就上去吧
English breakfast.
English Breakfast （英式早餐）
Alright!
好的
Today's breakfast is the unrecognizable English breakfast.
今天的早餐是面目全非的英式早餐？
Everything else is overcooked like crazy, but the beans are undercooked.
全部都熟过头了 而豆子却不够熟
I boiled them for a long time and they're still like that.
我煮了很久但是还是这样
You should have let them sit in water for a few hours beforehand.
豆子应该在煮之前泡水几个钟头
Oh!
哦
So this is the breakfast table of the new bride, Oh Ha Ni.
所以这个就是新媳妇吴哈妮的早餐啊
What about coffee?
咖啡呢？
Coffee!
咖啡
The coffee tastes good.
咖啡还不错
Sorry.
对不起
That's right!
噢 对了
What is it?
什么啊
The lady gave it to me. She said to eat it with my hubby.
这是大婶给的 让我跟老公一起吃
It's good. Try it.
不错 试试吧
Yours!
你自己的
They say an apple in the morning is great! It's really good, right?
人们说早餐吃苹果很好真的不错 对吧
An apple and coffee on Sunday morning...
周末早餐是咖啡和苹果
Not bad.
不错
I'll really do well tomorrow.
明天我会做的更好的
I've cleaned the whole house.
屋子已经打扫好了
So...
所以
The next course you've planned out.
你计划的下一个东西
Huh?
嗯？
Picking out my clothes. Oh, there was washing the blankets.
选我的衣服 还有洗被子
Let's do that at night.
晚上再洗吧
You knew all about it?
你怎么都知道
Oh, this is it!
这个
English breakfast and coffee.
英式早餐还有咖啡
Great! It suits us perfectly!
太好了 很适合我们
And... I'll do the shopping early in the morning,
还有 早上要去超市
and pick out the freshest produce!
选些新鲜的材料
I'll come back and clean with Seung Jo.
然后跟胜祖一起打扫房子
I'll be a loved daughter-in-law and then...
做一个惹人爱的媳妇
Wash the blankets with the morning sunlight pouring down on us. With tons of bubbles!
早上在阳光的沐浴下一起洗被子还要很多泡泡
And once we're done, we'll go watch a movie.
好了呢 就一起去看电影
Oh, I'll pick out Seung Jo's clothes!
噢 还要选胜祖的衣服
A style that matches the autumn sunlight!
配上秋天的风格
What'll look good?
要选哪个呢
I'll search for it!
找找吧
You think with your mouth. I couldn't ignore it even if I wanted to.
你想的都是用嘴说的，我怎么可能不知道？
We've got to go watch a movie.
我们还要看电影
Yeah! Wait!
对 等等
How is your outfit no different than mine?
你的衣服跟我的有什么差别啊
Why?! It's pretty.
为什么 很好看嘛
What's so pretty about it? Everyone is staring.
有什么好看的 每个人都在看
It's pretty.
很好看
Hold on.
等一下
Hubby!
老公
What, wifey?
怎么了 老婆
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at Viki
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at www.Viki
Playful Kiss (Naughty Kiss) YouTube Version Episode 2 Preview
惡作劇之吻 YouTube 篇 第二篇预告
Here.
来
Practice. Injection practice.
练习 插针练习
Just one more time and I think I'll definitely remember!
多一次我就一定会记得的
Hey, what are you doing?!
喂 你做什么